New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files
1985-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Cole, Paul M.
6202
37.5 cubic feet
37.5 linear ft.
Records.
8255165
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 10, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Biographical / Historical
David Lawrence Cole was a graduate of Harvard University (BS., 1921) and Fairleigh Dickinson University (LL.B., 1924, LL.D., 1964.) Although he practiced law in Paterson, N.J. from 1926 until his death as senior partner in the law firm of Cole, Berman & Belksy, David Cole will chiefly be remembered for a distinguished career as a government arbitrator and mediator. In this field he served on numerous state and federal boards and in various governmental agencies. Cole was chairman of the New Jersey State Board of Mediation; a public member of Region 2, United States War Labor Board; and chairman of the Presidential Boards of Inquiry in the bituminous coal industry (1948) and in the longshore industry (1953, 1968). Cole was also a member or chairman of numerous Presidential Emergency Boards which settled disputes in the railroad and airline industries (1948-1958); the chairman of the conciliation service for the New York City transit service (1961-1965); director of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service (1952-1953); chairman of the New Jersey Governor's Committee on Public Utility Strike Service (1952-1953); member of the President's Labor-Management Advisory Committee (1961-1964); and member of the New York Governor's Public Employee Relations Committee (1966-1968), which established the New York State Public Employee Relations Board. Cole was also appointed as chairman of the President's Commission on Industrial Peace in 1973.
Beyond his public service, Mr. Cole was active as a counsel for employer groups in the textile industry (1926-1942) and as an impartial chairman for other labor-management contract disputes. He was also impartial arbitrator for the AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan (1954-1976), served as a visiting professor at the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University (1954-1955) and was Kestenbaum lecturer at Harvard in 1962. Mr. Cole was the author of INDUSTRIAL PEACE (1963).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6202 OH: New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Interviews Oral History on Minidiscs 6202 AV: New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Interviews Audio-Visual Materials 6202 P(d): New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Digital Photographs
Cole, Paul; New York State AFL-CIO; AFL-CIO
8255165
- Meeting Files, 1/8/91-3/20/91. (Box 1)
  - Pension Task Force, NYS AFL-CIO, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Jan. 8
  - IRRA Dinner, Albany Hilton, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Jan 8
  - Special Meeting w/ Ira Magazines AFT, 9th Floor Conference Room ,Washington D.C., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Jan 9, 9:00 a.m.
  - NYSCOVE, Ontario, CA, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Jan 9-13
  - Division for Youth Council Mtg. NYSUT, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Jan. 10 12:30p.m., 159 wolf road, 2nd Fl. Conference rooms A & B
  - Strategic Planning Meeting, NYC Office, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    March 4, 12:30 p.m.
  - HRDI and SCANS, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Jan 14, 10 a.m. 815 16th Street Room 405, Washington, D.C.
  - NYSUT combined Election Dsitrict Dinner, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Feb 11, 5:30 p.m. Little White House, 5877 Main Street, Williamsville, NY
  - Legislative commission on Science & Technology, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Jan 17
  - SCANS Meeting at Motorola's' Glavin Center for Continuing Ed., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Jan 17-18 Schaumburg, IL
  - Planning Meeting for May Conf. on Technology & the Workforce Assembly Speakers Conf. room (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Mtg., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Jan 24-27, Condado Plaza Hotel, San Juan, Puerto Rico
  - Cornell Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Jan 24-26, NYC
  - LeMoyne College, Speech, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Jan 29, 7p.m.
  - SCOVE Meeting with D. Sauers, State Ed. Bldg. Room 146, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Jan 30
  - Irish American Dinner, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Feb 1
  - NYCCLC Annual Lincoln's Birthday Waldorf- Astoria, grand Ballroom NYC, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Feb 2, 7 p.m.
  - Nat'l Bicentennial Competition on the Constitution Bill of Rights, Convention Ctr., Albany, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Feb 2
  - BCJA, Legislative Breakfast, Albany Hilton, Albany, NY, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Feb 4-5, 7:45 a.m.
  - Annual Legislative Breakfast NYS Public Employee conference Empire State Plaza, Mtg. Room 6, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Feb 5, 9 a.m.
  - LAW Conference w/ Stephanie Thompson DOL, Albany, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Feb 7 3 p.m.
  - Labor Legacy Meeting, Room 544. Bldg. 12, DOL, Albany, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Feb 7, 3 pm
  - Hungary Democratic League of Free Trade Unions Delegation, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Feb 8, 9 am
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting Gideon Putnam Hotel, Saratoga Springs, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Feb 8-9, 8:30 pm
  - Jobs for the Future National Advisory Group Boston, MA, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Feb 8, 10 am
  - AFT Futures Committees Sheraton Bal Harbour, FL, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Feb 11-12
  - AFL CIO Executive Council Meetings, Bal Harbour, FL, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Feb 15
  - NYSUT Western NY Political Action Committee Legislative Cocktail Reception, Niagara County Teacher Manor, Depew (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Feb 22, 4:30 pm
  - Niagara County Teachers, ED 3 Legislative Cocktail Party, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Feb 22, 4-6 pm
  - Niagara (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - NYSUT Committee of 100 Desmond Americana, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Feb 25
  - AFT Legislative/ Political Conference Mayflower Hotel, 1127 Connecticut Ave NW, Washington D.C., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    March 6&7
  - NYSCOVE Inn at the Century, Route 9, Latham, NY, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Feb 20, 10am
  - NYSCOVE inn at the Century, route 9, Latham, NY, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Feb 20
  - Ad-Hoc Committee On Tax Policy, 48 E. 21 Street, 12 Floor, NYC, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Mar 4, 9 am
  - Meeting with Edythe D. Conway, PhD (Occ. Ed) here, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    March 4
  - Staff Meeting w/ Mary Crayton, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    March 6, 9am
  - AFT Local President's Conference Mayflower Hotel, Washington D.C., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    March 8
  - Cornell Board of Trustees Statler Hotel, Ithaca, NY, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    March 8-9
  - United Way of NYS Legislative Breakfast, Albany Room, Empire State Plaza, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    March 12
  - United Way of NYS Board of Directors Meeting, 155 Washington Avenue, 4th Floor, Albany, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Mar 13, 8am
  - NYS AFL-CIO Legislative Conf. Empire State Convention Center, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    March 13, 12:30 pm
  - Central Labor Council Presidents Meeting, 100 S, Swan Street, Albany, NY, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    March 13, 9:30 am
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1991 Legislative Conference, Empire State Convention Center (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Mar 13
  - Industrial Division Meeting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Mar 14
  - NYSUT Joint Election District Mtg., Airport Holiday Inn, 4600 Genesee Street, Cheek towaga, NY, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Mar. 15, 7:30pm
  - NYS AFL-CIO Congressional Breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Mar 20, 8am
  - NYSUT 1991 Federal Legislative Recept, Washington D.C. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Mar. 20
  - March, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Meeting Files, 9/5/91-11/7/91. (Box 2)
  - Labor Legacy Meeting, Here, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Sep 5, 2:30 pm
  - Hank Landau Reitrement Dinner, Michael's Banquet House, Latham, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Sept 5
  - Vermont State Labor Council, AFL-CIO 35th Annual Convention, Holiday Inn Rutland, VT, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Sept 13-15
  - Meeting w/ Tim Reilly, Uup 159 Wolf Road, Albany, NY; Re: Higher Education, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Sept 10, 12 pm
  - United Way of NYS Long Range Strategic Planning Committee, United Way of NYS, 155 Washington Ave, Albany, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Sept 11, 12 pm
  - Division for Youth, 52 Washington Street, Rensselear, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Sept 12
  - NYS Council of Machinists, Alex Bay, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Sept 13-14
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting Hilton Hotel, Albany, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Hilton Hotel, Albany, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Industrial Div. Conference Sheraton Inn, Syracuse, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Sept 15-17
  - NYS Dept. of Education, Dr. Nolan Cultural Education Building, 5th Floor Room 5B28, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Sept 18, 1pm
  - Secretary of the Interior, National Park Services, 18 & C. Street, NW Washington D.C. Room 3004, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Sept 19, 9:30 am
  - HRDI, 815 16th Street, NW Washington D.C., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Sept 19, 10 am
  - SCANS Education Meeting Holiday Inn Crowne Plaza, Arlington, VA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Sept 19, 3pm
  - SCANS Meeting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Sept 20
  - NYSUT ED 11-12 Meeting Amsterdam Holiday Inn, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Sept 21, 9 am
  - State Education Department Curriculum Assessment Council, Holiday Inn Crowne Plaza, 1065 Broadway, NYC, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Sept 24- 25, 5 pm
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Meeting Pittsburgh Hilton & Towers,, Pittsburgh, PA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Sept 25-27
  - HRDI "The Central Role of Skill Formation and Workplace Learning Systems," DuPont Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Sept 27, 9am
  - Auburn CLC Meeting, Auburn, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Oct. 1, 6:30 pm
  - Secretary of the Interior, National Park System Advisory Board, Colorado, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Oct 4-10
  - Secretary of the Interior, National Park System Advisory Board, Colorado, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cornell University ILR Advisory Council Capital Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Oct 7, 8:30
  - New Designs for the Comprehensive High School, Xerox Headquarters, El Sagundo, Los Angeles, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Oct 7-8
  - The task Force on Creating Career Pathways for New York's Youth, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Oct 7
  - Jobs for the Future, Parker House, Boston, MA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Oct 8
  - NYSUT Retiree Leadership Conf., Albany, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Oct 10
  - IRRA Dinner, Albany Hilton, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Oct 15, 6 pm
  - NYSUT Occupational Education Comm., Desmond Americana, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Oct 18, 10 am
  - Montana Federation of Teacher's Conference, Cooperking & butte Vo-tech Center, Butte Montana, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Oct 17-18
  - Advisory Council of the ILR Cornell Inst. For Labor Market Policies Statler Hotel, Ithaca, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Oct 20
  - AFT Executive Council, Hotel Hershey, Hershey, PA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Oct 21-23
  - AFT Civil and Human Rights Conference Hyatt Regency Hotel, Washington D.C., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Oct 25-27
  - NYSUT WNYPAC Meeting RO 270 Essjay Road, Centerpointe Corp. Park, Williamsville, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Oct 29, 7 pm
  - Creating Career Pathways Task Force Meeting, NYSUT Headquarters, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Oct 31, 10:30 am
  - AFT Vocational Education Comm., Washington D.C., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Nov 1-2, 10 am
  - AFT Vocational Education Comm., Washington D.C., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Nov 1-2, 10am
  - New York State Council on Vocational Education Meeting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Nov 4&5
  - New York State council on Vocational Education Meeting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    Nov 4-5, 2 of 2
  - Jefferson/Lewis Central Labor Council Clearview Restaurant Governor, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Nov 6, 7pm
  - Clarkson University, Potsdam, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Nov 6, 12pm
  - Massena Job Service Employer Committee, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Nov 7, 8-10 am
- Meeting Files, 11/7/91-12/9/94. (Box 3)
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Nov7-9
  - AFL-CIO Convention, Detroit, MI, The Westin Hotel, Detroit, MI, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Nov 10-16
  - National Park Service Dept of Interior Main building, 18 & C Streets, NW Room 3119, Washington, D.C., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Nov 19
  - Labor in the Schools, NYSUT Office 7 Ellinwood Court, N Hartford, NY, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Labor Legacy Meeting Russell Sage College, Troy, NY, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Nov 20, 3:30pm
  - International Affairs Conference Sheraton Center Hotel, royal Ballroom, 2nd Floor, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Dec 6
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting Desmond Americana, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Dec 6-7, 6pm
  - SCANS Meeting, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University, Symposium, J. Willard Marriott Exec. Educ. Ctr., Ampitheater, Statler Hotel, Ithaca, NY, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Dec 11, 4-6 pm
  - New Designs For the Comprehensive high School, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Dec 13-14
  - OSHA Tuberculosis in the Workplace Workshop, Albany Hilton Hotel, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Dec 16, 9 am
  - Operating Engineers Xmas Party Sheraton New York, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Dec 18, 12pm
  - Annual Message to the Legislature Rm. 250, P/U Tickets Seat by 12:30 Assembly Chamber, State Capitol, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Labor Legacy Meeting, Here, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Jan 9, 3:30pm
  - Career Pathways Task Force Mtg. 1515 Broadway, 52nd Floor New York, NY, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Jan 9, 10:45 am
  - Shield's Funeral, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Jan 11, 10 am
  - IRRA Meeting, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Jan 14, 6 pm
  - Curriculum and Assessment council, Manhattan Holiday inn, Crowne Plaza, New York, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Jan 14, 5pm
  - Jobs for the Future, Copley plaza Hotel, Boston, MA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Jan 15
  - Division for Youth, Youth Employ Advisory Council, 52 Washington Street, Rensselear, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Jan 16, 11 am
  - New designs for the Comprehensive high School, Atlanta, GA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    March 6-7
  - Mary Crayton, Albany Office, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    april 3
  - Employee Benefits Issue Briefs, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    April-Sept
  - National Training Board, National Competency Standards: Policy and Guidelines, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Second edition, October 1992.
  - AFL-CIO Position Paper on Unemployment Insurance, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    December, 1992
  - Insurance Reform Committee Task Force on Health Care Finance Reform, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    January 7, 1993
  - Photographs, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Workers Compensation Meeting, 48 E 21st Street, NYC, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    April 15, 1994.
  - Empire State Report, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    May, 1994.
  - Labor Management committee Workers Comp, 152 Washington Avenue, albany, NY, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    May 16, 1994.
  - Workers Comp LMC Painters District council 45 West 14th Street, New York City, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    May 20, 1994.
  - Workers Comp Labor-Management Committee, 180 Livingston Street, Room 600C, Brooklyn NYC, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    April 20, 1994.
  - Workers Compensation Labor-Management Meeting, DOL, 34th Street, NYC, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    June 6, 1994.
  - New York State AFL-CIO 27th Constitutional Convention, Proposed Amendments, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    July 29, 1994.
  - Labor-Management Committee Worker's Compensation, Business council, 152 Washington Ave, Albany, NY, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    June 320, 1994.
  - Labor Management committee, Workers compensation, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    September 26, 1994.
  - Labor Management committee Meeting: Workers' compensation, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    November 17, 1994.
  - Workers' comp Managed Care Prog. LMC, 152 Washington Avenue, Alb., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    December 9, 1994.
- Meeting Files, 9/13/94-1/24/95. (Box 4)
  - LRI Workplace Success Skills, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Sept 13
  - AFT Executive Council, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Oct 2-5
  - AFT Executive Council, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local Partnership Subcommittee JTPC Conference Room, Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Oct 13
  - NYSUT Board of Directors, Desmond, Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Oct 14-15
  - Governor's Conference on The Future of the Economy Sheraton Centre Hotel, NYC, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Oct 19
  - Meeting with Steve Hamilton & Mary Agnes Hamilton Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University Committee on Land Grant and Statutory College Aff. Statler Hotel, Pennsylvania Room, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Oct 20, 3 pm
  - Comm on Academic Affairs & Campus Life Taylor Salons 9 dinner) Rowe Room (Meeting till 9:30pm), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Staff Meeting. Sheraton Manhattan Conference Room 6, 5th Floor New York City, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Oct 12
  - Cornell Board of Trustees Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Oct 20-23
  - Symposium Sponsored by the Un at the Albany School of Education & the Rockefeller Inst., 411 State St., Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Business/Labor/Education Day VATEA, holiday Inn, Johnstown, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - WNY Educational conference Fall Event, Sheraton Inn, Buffalo Airport, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - School to Work Advisory committee Retreat, Thornwood Conf. Center Thornwood, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Oct 20-21
  - NYS Division for Youth, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Oct 21
  - Second Annual NY Statewide Tech Prep Conference, ESP Convention, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Oct 23-24
  - United Way of NYS Board & Committee Meetings as NYSUT, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Oct 26-27
  - Curriculum & Assessment Council Marriott Marquis, 1533 Broadway, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Oct 31
  - US Dept of Ed & The European Union 2 days Conference, Lowes Coronado Bay Resort, San Diego, CA, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Nov 3-4
  - Room at the Sheraton Centre, New York City, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Nov 8
  - NYSUT Community College President Fall Conference, Gideon Putnam Saratoga Springs, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Nov 12
  - Capital District union Label & Service Trades Council, Desmond Hotel, Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Oct 29
  - Labor Legacy Network 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Nov 16
  - Northeast Public Employees Conference, Trump Taj Mahal Casino Resort, Atlantic City, NJ, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Nov 20-22
  - Meeting w/ Bob Poczik, Room 307 EB, Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Nov 29
  - NYSCOVE, LaGuardia Comm. College & UFT Headquarters New York, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Dec 1-2
  - National Council on Economic Education Annual Awards Dinner, Sheraton Manhattan, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Dec 1
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Mtg. Sheraton, NY Versailles Terrace, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Dec 2-3
  - National Board for Professional Teaching Standard, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Dec 2-4
  - NYS Job Training Partnership Council, Cornell University ILR, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Dec 5
  - Jobs for the Future Advisory Committee, Park House, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Alcohol and Drug Testing on the Job An overview of the new US DOT Regulations, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Dec 8
  - NYSUT Statewide Conference on In-service Education, Desmond Albany, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Dec 10-11
  - Youth Fair Chance National Adv. Panel Meeting, KRA Corp., 1010 Wayne Ave., Suite 850, Sliver Springs, MD, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Dec 13, 9am
  - NPS, Washington D.C., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Dec 14
  - AFT Vocational Education Task Force, Hyatt Regency Washington, 400 New Jersey Avenue, NW Washington D.C., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Dec 15-17
  - School-to-work Advisory Comm. Meeting Room 2, Empire State Plz. Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Dec 21
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Meeting Caribe Hilton, San Juan, PR, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Jan 6-19
  - Labor Legacy Meeting, Here, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Jan 19
  - Industrial Division, Steering committee Meeting, 100 S. Swan Street, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - JFF Briefing on Promising Practices A Study of Ten School-to-Career Programs, 2261 Rayburn HOB Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Jan 23
  - NYATEP/AFL-Competing, Omni hotel Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Jan 24
- Meeting Files, 1/25/95-5/22/95. (Box 5)
  - Alcohol & Drug Testing: An Overview of the New US DOT Regulations, Quality Inn, Albany, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Jan 25
  - JTPC School-to-work Adv. Comm. Omni Hotel, Capitol room, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Jan 25-26
  - School-to-work Technical Assist Conference, Omni Hotel, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Meeting with LMC Advisors, New York City Offices, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Jan 26
  - SEFA Meeting Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NYSCOVE, Heritage Inn, Southington, CT, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Feb 3
  - DED Meeting, State Campus, Bldg. 12 Room 400, Albany, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Gideon Putnam Hotel & conference Center, Saratoga Springs, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Feb 3-4
  - UFT Retiree Chapter, "Molly Maguire's" 49 E 21 Street, 2nd Floor, New York, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Feb 8
  - AFT Executive Council Sheraton Bal Harbour Florida, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Feb 14-16
  - AFL-CIO Winter Meetings Sheraton Bal Harbour, FL, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Feb 20-24
  - JTPC School to Work Advi Comm NYSUT Room B Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Feb 24
  - NYSUT WNY PAC Legislative Cocktail Party, Salvatore's Ital. Rest. 6461 Transit Road, Depew, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Labor Legacy Meeting, Russell Sage College, Conference Center Troy, New York, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Feb 28
  - UWNYS Board of Directors, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    March 1-2
  - NYSCOVE Culinary Institute of America Hyde Park, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    March 2-3
  - National Comm. For Cooperative Education, Board of Trustees Mtg. Princeton Club 15 W 43rd Street, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    March 6
  - Joint Public Hearing Moratorium on Proposed Rules & Regs., Hearing Rm. B, LOB, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - IATSE Local 14 100th Anniversary the Desmond, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    March 11
  - United Way Meeting w/ Comm Daly, SOC, Building 5, Fifth Floor, Albany, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    March 13
  - NYSUT Local Presidents Conf. Hyatt Regency Rochester, Rochester, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    March 15-16, 1 of 2
  - NYSUT Local President's Conf. Hyatt Regency Rochester, Rochester, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    March 15-16, 2 of 2
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, New York, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    March 16-17
  - New York City Central Labor Council Awards Dinner, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    March 18
  - NYS Legislative Conference Empire State Plaza, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    March 22
  - NYS AFL-CIO Staff Meeting Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Onondaga County Umbrella Grant Showcase Workshop Day, Onondaga Community College, Syracuse, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    March 23